# **REUT ROSENFELD**

## CONTACT

- **2** 050-294-4421
- ✓ reutroz@gmail.com
- Barqan, Israel

### ABOUT ME

I am experienced in the field of national security, with 10 years of service: serving in IDF as a combat soldier, working for private security companies and serving in Israel Police as a cadet.

I have excellent interpersonal communication skills, and my previous jobs required the ability to take initiative, solve complicated and unexpected problems, excel and be creative.

These days, I am in the midst of retraining in the field of Full-Stack Web Development.

## LANGUAGES

Hebrew



English

## SKILLS

- Problem-Solving
- Self-Learning
- Quick-learner
- Strong Communication
- Leadership
- Decision-making
- Team-management

## EDUCATION

## STUDENT FOR FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

Hacker-U College (2024)

## **B.A. FOR CRIMINOLOGY & MIDDLE EAST STUDIES**

Ariel University (2020-2023)

#### HIGH-SCHOOL DIPLOMA

Ort Qiryat Bialik (2011-2014)

- Certificate for Social Excellence.
- Graduated from a leadership development program.
- Studied the "Michael Method", for fulfilling the individual potential to attain excellence.

## EXPERIENCE

#### **POLICE OFFICER**

Israel Police

#### 2021-2024

- Served as a "Shoham" cadet, a reserve program for outstanding academics.
- Worked as a patrol officer, which required handling difficult crime scenes, assertiveness, reliability and composure in stressful situations.

#### **SECURITY GUARD**

Private companies

## 2018-2021

- Security guard at the National Social Security Institute of Israel.
- Security guard at "CanBreed", a highly secured lab-farm for research, production and development of cannabis seeds.
- · Both jobs included an advanced security guard training.

#### **ARMY SERVICE**

Israel Defense Forces

## 2014-2017

- Serving as a combat soldier for 36 months.
- Promotion to a command position without previous experience or training.
- Discharged with honor and a noteworthy rating.